chiefsupply.com 2006-06-16

# Privacy & Security Policy - CHIEF

**CHIEF HOME**  
**Meet the new CHIEF!**

**ABOUT CHIEF**  
**Sitemap**  
**Why Shop CHIEF?**  
**Company Profile**  
**Testimonials**  
**In the News**  
**Career Opportunities**  
**Contact Us**

* * *

**HELP**  
**FAQ**  
**Shipping Charges and Delivery Times**  
**Returns**  
**Free Catalog**  
**Affiliate Program**  
»» **Privacy Policy**  

* * *

**RESOURCES**  
**MSDS**  
**Fire Glossaries**  
**Industry Links**  
**Download Catalog**  
**Newsletter**  
**CHIEF Grants**

**Contact Us**

|    | 

### _Privacy & Security Policy_

### Simply Put

  * We don't spam.
  * Your personal information stays put. We don't distribute it to third parties
  * Ordering from CHIEFsupply.com is safe and secure: We use industry-standard encryption technologies and physical security measures to protect your personal and financial information
  * Browsing and ordering via CHIEFsupply.com will not result in your computer getting infected by spyware, adware or viruses
  * We do not phish, pharm or participate in any illicit or identity theft activities, whether or not they start with "ph"
  * CHIEFsupply.com will never ask for your Social Security Number
  * All CHIEF email newsletters and fax promotions include unsubscription instructions. Again, we don't distribute your email address, fax number, or any other information to third parties.

**If at any time you have a complaint or concern about CHIEF, pleasecontact us.**

### Contact Information

This is the web site of **CHIEF**. 

Our postal addresses are:   
**P.O. Box 481912  
Charlotte, NC 28269**

**1400 Executive Parkway / Suite 220 / Mailbox 26  
Eugene, OR 97401**

We can be reached via e-mail at this address or you can reach us by telephone at (800) 824-4338 from 5am - 4pm, PT, Weekdays. 

### Full Details & Required Legal Speak

**Security**  
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

**What We Track and Don't Track**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 

We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as catalog requests or on-line orders. 

**How We Use Contact Information**  
The information we collect is used to notify consumers about issues with his or her order or if they have opted in to our newsletter, updates to our Web site. 

When we offer contests, promotions or feedback surveys, you may be required to provide certain personal information in order to participate. In these cases, we will give you the choice not to receive email messages or other communications from us regarding our products, services, contests, and promotions. We may use your contact information to reach you about the sweepstakes or contest. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart. To purchase off of our Web site, the user must enable cookies. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above or by e-mailing us at the above address. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

**Fax Privacy & Opt-In**  
In compliance with FCC regulations in effect as of June 30, 2005, CHIEF has a faxable, downloadable opt-in form (MS Word format). By filling out and returning this form to CHIEF, you "opt in" to receiving fax promotions from CHIEF. Should you wish to change your fax preferences in the future, all fax promotions from CHIEF include instructions on how to unsubscribe. 

Whether or not you choose to receive promotions from CHIEF, we protect your privacy and do not sell or rent your information with third parties. 

**Updates to Privacy Policy**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically (we will maintain a last-updated date at the bottom of this web page). 

**How You Can Access or Update Your Information**  
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by writing to us at the 1400 Executive Parkway, Suite 220/ Mailbox 26, Eugene, OR 97401. Consumers can have this information corrected by calling us at (800) 824-4338 from 5am - 4pm, PT, Weekdays. 

**If You Would Like to File a Complaint**  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at [mgoldberger@the-dma.org](mailto:mgoldberger@the-dma.org), state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>.

_Last Updated: June 30, 2005_
